Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance and Society records, 1960-2006; Series 2
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Bill, Undated; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence with William J. Reese, 1978-1989; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between WIlliam J. Reese and Mark A. Kalthoff, October 19, 1987; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Mrs. Berson, 1982; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Nancy Green, October 21, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor Barry M. Franklin, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor Christine Heward, September 29, 1988; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor Thomas James, May 25, 1988; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor John R. Shinners, Jr., January 14, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor David Hogan, October 27, 1987; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor Steven A. Gelb, February 9, 1989; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor Steven A. Gelb, September 14, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Professor William W. Cutler, June 24, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Richard Altenbaugh, August 14, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Steve Crum, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and T.G. August, September 18, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between William J. Reese and Ulla Johnson, October 10, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between William Irwin Thompson and Paul H. Mattingly, November 3, 1973; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Allan S. Horlick, May 2, 1972; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Paul Mattingly, February 21, 1979; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Paul, September 19, 1979; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Sol Cohen, March 3, 1981; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Willis Rudy and Paul Mattingly, March 25, 1983; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between William R. Keylor to Paul Mattingly, March 10, 1979; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between William W. Cutler and Ms. Amy Schott, September 11, 1988; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between William L. Blackwell and Professor Mattingly, May 11, 1978; Series 2 (Box 63, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Paul H. Mattingly, June, 1972; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Paul H. Mattingly, September 21, 1972; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Paul H. Mattingly, July 4, 1973; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Wilson Smith and Paul H. Mattingly, August 1, 1974; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Tasukatsu Ohno and Robin Berson, 1984, 1985; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence -- Directors, Board, Officers, 1992-1995; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Council of learned societies in education, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Council of Learned Societies in Education, 1985, 1987, 1988; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - The Count/Beard Correspondence, April 19, 1978; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Cultural conflict in cultural public schools, 1973; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Curriculum in religious education course requirements, 1973; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Curriculum vita - Gidney, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Curriculum vitae - Goodenow, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Curriculum vitae of Gwyneth Dow, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - David Churchill Humphrey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Denhard and Stewart, 1981, 1982; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - Department of religious education, January 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - The Dorothy B. Sutherland Group, 1982; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Draft - on development of current master's program, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Draft of proposed preamble, November 30, 1972; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Editorial Board, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - Editorial list, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 84)
  - Education Foundation of America annual report, 1982; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Education Society, 1968; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 86)
  - Education and society in modern France, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Education theory education building, September 28, 1972; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 88)
  - Educators immigrants, February 1973; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - E.G. Vallianatos, August 30, 1972; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Election results of History of Education Society, April 20, 1972; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Elections 1987, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment of students in schools, 1826-1840, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Essay review flow sheet, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Eugene P. Link letters, 1973, 1974; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Expenses incured as corporate delegate to the biennial convention, June 1973; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - External review of HEQ - 1990, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Faculty of arts and sciences, 1972; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Faculty of education student committee, 1973; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Faculty welfare committee, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Fall 1967 History of Education Quarterly, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Faxon urgent cancellation, November 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Financial Report, 1985, 1986; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Financial reporting, 1984, 1985; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Financial reports, 1984-2008; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Financial reports - HES - 1981-1984, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Fine arts and religion, 1973; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Founding conference, February 14, 1980; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Foundations of education, December 5, 1973; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Guidelines for writing of family history, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Hampel's sketch of HES (2008), Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Harvard University Gazette, October 29, 1976; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - H. L. Warm Schupf's resume, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - HEQ 1987 - 88 - 89, 1987, 1988, 1989; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - HEQ correspondence from president, board of directors, 1987, 1988, 1989; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - HEQ finances - SRU, 2004, 2005; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - HEQ financial reports, 1980-1992, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - HEQ - Indiana Univ. corresp. (mostly $), 1986, 1987, 1988; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - HEQ Newsletter, 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - HEQ - Slippery Rock applications, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - HES, 1960-1962, 1976, 1989; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - HES 1979, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - HES Bank, January 1989; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - HES board directors 1979-81, 1979-1981; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - HES; call for papers, Undated; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - HES elections, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - HES - Elections - 1985, June 1985; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - HES - Elections - 1986, October 10, 1986; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - HES Elections 1986, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - HES Elections 1988, Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - HES to file, 1988, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - HES general inquiries, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - HES Income 1985/86, 1985, 1986; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - HES Income 1986/87, 1986, 1987; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - HES Income 1987/88, 1987, 1988; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - HES Income 1989/90, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - HES Income 1990/91, 1990, 1991; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - HES misc. inquiries 1985/88, June 29, 1987; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - HES membership lists, 1984, 1985; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - HES International Standing Conference, 1983, 1986-1989; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - HES paid bills Jan 1985-June 30, 1985, Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - HES paid bills, 1985-86, 1985, 1986; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - HES paid bills 86/87, 1986, 1987; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - HES paid bills 87/88, 1987, 1988; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - HES paid bills 88/89, 1988, 1989; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - HES paid bills 89/90, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - HES program additions and corrections, October 19; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - HES Quarterly, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1985; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - HES Quarterly and Ezri Atzmon, Undated; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - HES - Renewal notices etc., 1985, 1986; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - HES report of financial aspects of annual meeting, Oct. 9-11, 1987, Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Hierarchy and consensus, 1973; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Hiner's History of HES (1990), Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - History of Education and Culture, Undated; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - History of Education meeting 1989, Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - TheHistory of Education meeting of the American Educational Research, 1970; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - History of Education meeting of the board of directors, October 26, 1973; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - History of Education newsletter, Undated; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1961; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1967; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1967; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1968; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1968; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1968, 1969, 1970; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1969; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1970; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - History of Education Quarterly, January 22, 1975; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1978; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1979; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - History of Education Quarterly, 1983; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - History of Education Quarterly, Undated; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Higher Education Quarterly Review Process, 1983; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - History of Education Quarterly [Review Prompt], 1982; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - History of Education Society, 1965; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Society, 1968; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Society, 1969; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Society, 1970-1973; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - History of Education Society, 1976; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - History of Education Society, 1976, 1978; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - History of Education Society, 1977; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Society, 1978; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Society, October 2, 1981; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - History of Education Society, 1982; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - History of Education Society, 1982; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - History of Education Society, Undated; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - History of Education Society, Undated; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - History of Educ. Society 60s/70s, 1961-1981; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - History of Education Society Membership list, December 10, 1962; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - History of Education Society Membership list, 1966; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - History of Education Society membership list, 1973; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - History of Education Society Office of Secretary-Treasurer, 1967; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - History of Education Society Office of the Secretary-Treasurer, 1973; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - History of Education Society Office of the Secretary-Treasurer, 1977; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - History of Education Society officers and committee, 1980-81, Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - History of Higher Education Annual; call for manuscripts, September 5, 1984; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - History of TTT, 1972; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Improving high schools humanities teaching: problems, issues, and possibility, Undated; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Income 1988/89, 1988, 1989; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Interchange: a journal of educational studies, 1972; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Interim Report 1986, May 2, 1986; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1981-1986, 1992; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - International, 1988, 1990; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - International newsletter for the history of education, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - International Standing Conference, September 1984; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - International, 1985-1987, 1992; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - IRS, 1981-1986; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - IRS to do/or important, 1985, 1990; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Jan. 1970-Feb. 1971, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Jane Adams and the first generation of college women, Undated; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - James Mills and the era of reform, 1973; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - John Locke's teaching machine, 1973; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - JHU, Elbaum, T+F proposalsto publish HEQ, 2002-2004; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - John Locke: education and the 17th century constitutional crisis, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Journal of the midwest HES and David L. Angus, March 12, 1982; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Journal of the midwest history of educaton society, 1979; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - June 1966-Aug 1966, Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Kathleen C. Berkeley's resume, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Kent State University libraries invoice, 1984; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Leaders in education, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Library list, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Linking home and school, 1973; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Loose ends, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Loose in box, 1972, 1973; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Lynn Dorothy Gordon, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mailings requirements section History of Education Quarterly, June 1966; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Manuscripts for summer, 1984 issue, June 12, 1984; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Mar. 1971-Sept. 1971, Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - March-August 1972, Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Membership lists 60s, 1963-1965, 1969; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Memorandum to GSO, January 24, 1974; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Memorandum to the education recording office, November 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Memorandum to reader services, Bobst Library, October 22, 1974; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Memorandum to Mr. Robert Ritter, July 3, 1968; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Memorandum of revision of constitution of the History of Education Society, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Memorandum to students in E70 2003 religious education of children, December 12, 1974; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Ment's accounts, 1985-1990; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Midtown letter charges made in 1973, Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Minutes, 1984-2007, Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors + Business 1987, October 9, 1987; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Minutes of History of Education Society, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Minutes of the History of Education Society, February 25, 1972; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Business, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Names and info, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - National History of Education Society Business Meeting, October 27, 1973; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - The National Society for the Study of Communications, May 8, 1968; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Nature, Education, and the National Woman, 1973; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - The Network, 1984-1988; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - The Network, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Nominees of HES, 1981; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Notices, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - NYU School of Education bibliography, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Order for fall 1967 issue, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Order for spring 1964 Issue, Undated; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Paid bills, 1985-1990; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Patrol Relations Section, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, July 15, 1971; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Paul H. Mattingly letters, 1972, 1974, 1981, 1983; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Periods in Komodore's art, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Peter Dobkin Hall citations for AERA transcript, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Planning dinner meeting, July 1974; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Popular subscription service invoice, 1984; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Post office schemes and schedules section, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Pres, VP duties - "Manual", Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Prizes, 1989, 1990; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Prizes 1987, 1988, Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Prof. Goodenow's vitae, April 2, 1979; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Prof. Michael C. Coleman correspondences, 1986-1988; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for national historical publication and records commission, May 1, 1978; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Psychohistory and psychotherapy, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Reese-HEQ correspondence 89-91, 1985, 1987-1991; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Reese misc., 1986-1992; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Register of copyrights Library of Congress, 1964; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Religious education of children course requirements, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Religious education fellowship, September 18, 1970; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Religious education fellowship of the Department of Religious Education, October 20, 1972; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Report, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Report of HES Meetings, 1981, 1082; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Report of meeting of board of directors, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Research studies and development in the arts, July 14, 1969; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Responses to newsletter questionnaire, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Responses to questions listed in the margins, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Resume - Berson, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Resume - Komodore, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Resume - Stolpen, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Resume - Weber, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Reviewers sent books previously, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Richard M. Rollin's resume, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - The rise of college, May 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Rockefeller Archives Center invoice, May 1985; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Roderic AI Camp's resume, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - San Francisco of the 1930s and its program for mentally retarded children, 1973; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - School of Education, Undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - School of Education Department of Education, January 17, 1974; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - School of Education History Department, 1971, 1972; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Scripps College School of Education, September 1973; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Sept. 1966-May 1967, 1966, 1967; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 1)
  - Service on Dissertation Committees, February 11, 1971; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 2)
  - Sept. 1971-March 1972, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 3)
  - Service to HES, 1992- award winners, undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 4)
  - Sidell Independent School District, November 28, 1972; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 5)
  - Sociology of religion, Undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 6)
  - Sociology of religion course requirements, Undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 7)
  - Southern History of Education Society newsletter, 1979; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 8)
  - Spencer and Goodchild paper 2010, Undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 9)
  - Sputnik in American, 1973; Series 2 (Box 36, Box 10)
  - Stanford University School of Education, March 10, 1970; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Stephenie G. Edgerton Letters, 1972; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Stephenie G. Edgerton letters, 1972, 1973; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Student employee classification system, 1976, 1978; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Student initiative for curricular change, Undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Studies in philosophy and education, August 23, 1967; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Subscription from David Ment to Gertrude Ansovou, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Acadia University Ltd, 1984; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Christa Teutsch, March 15, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to College of Education University of Florida, July 11, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Findley Memorial Library, 1984; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Indiana University, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Juliet Junior College, 1984; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly by King Sejong University Library, 1984, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Library of Michigan, 1984; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Robin Berson, 1984; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Robin Berson, May 9, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Robin Berson, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Subscription from History of Education Society to Salisbury campus Australia, 1985; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to School of Education, University of Michigan, Undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Subscription from History of Education Quarterly to Southern Illinois University, 1984; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Subscription from international subscription agencies by Robin Berson, 1983; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 32)